A Guide to the Simpson family photographs, Series 1069 FA464
Rockefeller Archive Center
Simpson family photographs, Series 1069
1919-1939
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Simpson, Paul
FA464
0.2 Cubic Feet 1 clamshell box.
Scope and Contents note
Acadia, State Parks, Bridges, Maine, National Parks, Road Construction.
File Titles provide the image number followed by a description of the item.
Most of the photographic images were taken by Paul D. Simpson, and many of the descriptions were created directly by the Simpson family.
Biographical/Historical note
Charles P. Simpson was born in Sullivan, Maine, near Mount Desert Island, on September 19, 1848. At the age of twenty he headed West, learning the science of engineering in California. He later settled in Nebraska where he became a land surveyor and part owner in a sawmill and lumberyard. Simpson married Mary Walworth, of Zanesville, Ohio, in 1874. In 1880 they and their three children returned to Sullivan, and Simpson established an engineering and surveying office. He began working for John D. Rockefeller, Jr., in 1913, continuing as Rockefeller's chief engineer for the Seal Harbor carriage roads until he became ill in 1922. Charles P. Simpson died in 1928.
Paul Dyer Simpson, Charles P. Simpson's son, took over as Rockefeller's chief engineer at the time of his father's illness. Born March 10, 1876, in St. Paul, Nebraska, Paul Simpson began his engineering training while working in his father's surveying office in Sullivan. After serving in the Army during the Spanish-American War he graduated from the University of Maine in 1903 with a degree in civil engineering. He then worked in the West for eight years for the U.S. Reclamation Service. Upon his return to Maine in 1912 he again joined his father in the surveying business. After succeeding his father as Rockefeller's chief engineer in 1922 he continued in that role until 1940, when the roads were incorporated in Acadia National Park. He then served as a consulting engineer for the Rockefeller family until he retired in 1954. Paul D. Simpson died at Seal Harbor in 1963.
The Seal Harbor carriage road system was begun in 1915 when John D. Rockefeller, Jr., already building roads on his private summer estate, received permission from the Hancock County Trustees of Public Reservations to continue the roads across land which they maintained. The system eventually embraced a 57-mile network of carriage roads laced with sixteen bridges. The chief architects for the roads were Rockefeller, who laid out the initial line for each road, the two Simpsons, and Walters G. Hill, also a local engineer. The first ten bridges were designed by Welles Bosworth, the remaining six by Charles Stoughton, both New York City architects. The roadside landscaping was planned by Beatrix Farrand, who also designed Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's garden at the Eyrie in Seal Harbor.
Most of the roads were completed by 1930, at which time Rockefeller began the gradual transfer of his property to Acadia National Park. The transfer was concluded in the early 1940s. Rockefeller ultimately presented Acadia National Park with 10,700 acres, one-third of the park's size.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids note
For the Simpson family papers please see:
FA073 Simpson family papers
Arrangement
As received.
- Simpson family photographs, 1919-1939; bulk; 1069; 0.2 Cubic Feet 1 clamshell box.
  - 1: 1928 Nash car used by Paul D. Simpson. Used in 1940's by son, Chip, and was burned in fire of 1947. (Box 1)
  - 2: Carriage road on Jordan Mountain. (Box 1)
  - 3: Tumble-down around Jordan Pond. Breaking carriage road through rock slide. (Box 1)
  - 4: Carriage road around Eagle Lake (Box 1)
  - 4: View on Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road (Box 1)
  - 5: Paul D. Simpson with son, Chip, 1928. Chief engineer for JDR, Jr. during the work on the carriage roads, 1922-1941. (Box 1)
  - 6: Bridge construction on the Jordan Pond Road (carriage road underneath). Built in 1932. (Box 1)
  - 7: Lawn in front of Jordan Pond House with Jordan Pond and the Bubbles Mountain in background. (Box 1)
  - 8: Eagle Lake Bridge construction (Box 1)
  - 9: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 10: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 11: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 12: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 13: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 14: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 15: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 16: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 17: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 18: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 19: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 20: Constructing Jordan-Sargent Carriage Road. Jordan Pond. (Box 1)
  - 21: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 22: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 23: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 24: Derrick at construction of Deer Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 25: Hemlock Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 26: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 27: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 28: Construction of Mountain Road along east side of Jordan Pond (Box 1)
  - 29: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 30: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 31: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 32: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 33: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 35: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 36: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 37: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 38: Jordan-Sargent Mountain horse road - difficult construction across rockslide. (Box 1)
  - 39: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 40: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 41: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 42: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 43: Waterfall Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 44: Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road - construction on west side of Jordan Pond. (Box 1)
  - 45: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 46: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 47: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 48: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 49: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 50: Construction of water main from Jordan Pond to Seal Harbor, 1931-1932 (Box 1)
  - 51: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 52: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 53: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 54: Construction equipment used in building carriage roads and bridges (Box 1)
  - 55: JDR. Jr. corporation garage (for equipment). (Box 1)
  - 56: JDR. Jr. corporation garage (for equipment). (Box 1)
  - 57: JDR. Jr. corporation garage (for equipment). (Box 1)
  - 58: JDR. Jr. corporation garage (for equipment). (Box 1)
  - 59: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 60: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 61: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 62: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 63: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 64: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 65: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 66: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 67: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 68: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 69: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 70: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 71: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 72: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 73: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 74: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 75: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 76: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 77: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 78: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 79: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 80: Sites of lodges and tea houses (for JDR, Jr.). (Box 1)
  - 81: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 82: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 83: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 84: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 85: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 86: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 87: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 88: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 89: Jordan Pond gatehouse with Chip Simpson in front, 1934 (Box 1)
  - 90: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 91: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 92: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 93: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 94: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 95: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 96: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 97: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 98: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 99: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 100: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 101: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 102: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 103: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 104: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 105: Sample walls. (Box 1)
  - 106: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 107: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 108: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 109: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 110: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 111: Hemlock Bridge under construction. (Box 1)
  - 112: Hemlock Bridge under construction. (Box 1)
  - 113: Jordan Pond-Asticou Bridge #1 (West Branch Bridge). (Box 1)
  - 114: Bridge under construction. (Box 1)
  - 115: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 116: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 117: Waterfall Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 118: Bridge under construction. (Box 1)
  - 119: Cobblestone Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 120: Deer Brook Bridge on Jordan-Sargent Mountain horse road (Box 1)
  - 121: Waterfall Bridge on Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road. (Box 1)
  - 122: Hemlock Bridge. (Identified on back of photograph as East Lake Bridge) (Box 1)
  - 123: Waterfall Bridge on Jordan-Sargent Mountain horse road. (Box 1)
  - 124: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 125: Deer Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 126: Jordan Pond Bridge and view of Bubbles. (Box 1)
  - 127: Waterfall Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 128: Hemlock Bridge under construction. (Box 1)
  - 129: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 130: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 131: Hemlock Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 132: Jordan Pond Road Bridge after completion, 1932 (Box 1)
  - 133: Hemlock Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 134: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 135: Hemlock Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 136: Hemlock Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 137: Hemlock Bridge in Hadlock Pond Valley. (Box 1)
  - 138: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 139: Bubble Pond Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 140: Road (Box 1)
  - 141: View of park road. (Box 1)
  - 142: View from Chasm Brook Bridge on Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road. (Box 1)
  - 143: View of park road. (Box 1)
  - 144: View of frozen waterfall from park road. (Box 1)
  - 145: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 146: View from shore. (Box 1)
  - 147: Quarry ? (Box 1)
  - 148: Quarry ? (Box 1)
  - 149: View of park road. (Box 1)
  - 150: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 151: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 152: View of ice from park road. (Box 1)
  - 153: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 154: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 155: View of frozen waterfall from park road. (Box 1)
  - 156: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 157: View. (Box 1)
  - 158: Jordan Pond end of Jordan-Sargent-Mountain Road under construction. (Box 1)
  - 159: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 160: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 161: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 162: View of park road. (Box 1)
  - 163: View of park road. (Box 1)
  - 164: View from park road. (Box 1)
  - 165: Going south on Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road above Jordan Pond (Box 1)
  - 166: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 167: View on Mountain Road. (Box 1)
  - 168: View from carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 169: View from carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 170: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 171: View from carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 172: Unidentified man in woods. (Box 1)
  - 173: Unidentified man in woods. (Box 1)
  - 174: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 175: Unidentified building. (Box 1)
  - 176: Lake view. (Box 1)
  - 177: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 178: Lake view. (Box 1)
  - 179: Lake view. (Box 1)
  - 180: Jordan-Sargent Mountain horse road. West side Jordan Pond from mountain road eastside pond. (Box 1)
  - 181: View of carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 182: Unidentified boy (Chip Simpson?) on horseback. (Box 1)
  - 183: Mr. Payton, riding instructor at entrance to carriage road Jordan Pond. (Box 1)
  - 184: Mr. Rockefeller ? (Box 1)
  - 185: Unidentified man standing with cars. (Box 1)
  - 186: Charles P. Simpson, Sr., 1926 (Box 1)
  - 187: Charles "Chip" Simpson, age 5, with Mr. Payton, riding master at the old stables near entrance to carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 188: Mr. Payton and Chip Simpson, both on horseback. (Box 1)
  - 189: Chip Simpson on horseback, and Mr. Payton. (Box 1)
  - 190: Unidentified men in woods. (Box 1)
  - 191: Unidentified man in woods. (Box 1)
  - 192: Unidentified man posing with car. (Box 1)
  - 193: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 194: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 195: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 196: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 197: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 198: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 199: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 200: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 201: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 202: Unidentified construction site (depression in ground). (Box 1)
  - 203: Crane(?) covered in snow. (Box 1)
  - 204: Harbor Club, Seal Harbor, c. 1925-1926 (Box 1)
  - 205: Construction of pool, Seal Harbor yacht club. (Box 1)
  - 206: Carriage road crossing Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 207: Snow and ice on carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 208: Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road near Southwest Valley Pass (Box 1)
  - 209: View. (Box 1)
  - 210: Chip Simpson in front of Jordan Pond House, 1932-1933 (Box 1)
  - 211: View (Box 1)
  - 212: View (Box 1)
  - 213: View (Box 1)
  - 214: Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 215: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 216: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 217: Asticou-Jordan Pond Bridge #1 (West Branch Bridge). (Box 1)
  - 218: Jordan Stream Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 219: Cobblestone Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 220: Cobblestone Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 221: Bridge (Box 1)
  - 222: Bridge (Box 1)
  - 223: Bridge (Box 1)
  - 224: Bridge on Stanley Brook Road. (Box 1)
  - 225: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 226: Jordan-Sargent Mountain Road near Southwest Valley Pass (Box 1)
  - 227: View. (Box 1)
  - 228: Rockefeller Road and Jordan Mountain. (Box 1)
  - 229: Jordan Pond and Bubbles. (Box 1)
  - 230: Paul Simpson's car. (Box 1)
  - 231a: Paul Simpson's car. (Box 1)
  - 231b: JDR Jr. watching road construction. (Box 1)
  - 232: Duck Brook Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 233: Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 234: Work on Jordan Pond Road Bridge, 1931-1932 (Box 1)
  - 235: Jordan Pond Road and Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 236: Jordan Pond Road and Bridge construction, 1928. (Box 1)
  - 237: Duck Brook Bridge, detail of stone masonry. (Box 1)
  - 238: Duck Brook Bridge, detail of stone masonry. (Box 1)
  - 239: Mountain Road, east side Jordan Pond, under construction. (Box 1)
  - 240: Crane at construction scene. (Box 1)
  - 241: Road construction scene. (Box 1)
  - 242: Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 243: Steam shovel at construction scene. (Box 1)
  - 244: Steam roller at road construction. (Box 1)
  - 245: Steam roller at road construction. (Box 1)
  - 246: Steam roller at road construction. (Box 1)
  - 247: Steam roller at road construction. (Box 1)
  - 248: Steam shovel at construction scene. (Box 1)
  - 249: Tar truck spraying graveled road surface. (Box 1)
  - 250: Old tar truck near Bubble Pond-Mountain Road. (Box 1)
  - 251: Bar Hill-Day Mountain Road, footings for underpass bridge-Jordan Pond road. (Box 1)
  - 252: Moving coping stones along West Jordan Pond Road. (Box 1)
  - 253: Crane. (Box 1)
  - 254: Bridge construction, probably Jordan Pond Road Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 255: Rock slide on carriage road. (Box 1)
  - 256: Jordan Pond Road Bridge construction, 1932 (Box 1)
  - 257: Jordan Pond Road Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 258: Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 259: Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 260: Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 261: Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 262: Tarring road surface. (Box 1)
  - 263: Crane moving boulder. (Box 1)
  - 264: View on Bar Harbor-Seal Harbor motor road. On Pemetic Mountain looking at one of the Bubbles. (Box 1)
  - 265: One of the Bubbles from the mountain motor road. (Box 1)
  - 266: One of the Bubbles from the mountain motor road. (Box 1)
  - 267: Jordan Stream Bridge, south end of Jordan Pond. (Box 1)
  - 268: Amphitheater Bridge, Detail., 1931 (Box 1)
  - 269: Bridge on High Brook Road, Eagle Lake area. (Box 1)
  - 270: "Arch" Raven Cliff. (Box 1)
  - 271: Bridge on Stanley Brook Road. (Box 1)
  - 272: Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 273: IV3A10-273 Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 274: Bridge on Stanley Brook Road, 1928 (Box 1)
  - 275: Bridge on Stanley Brook Road, 1930 (Box 1)
  - 276: Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 277: Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 278: Duck Brook Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 279: Duck Brook Bridge construction. (Box 1)
  - 280: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 281: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 282: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 283: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 284: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 285: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 286: Duck Brook Bridge, detail of stone masonry. (Box 1)
  - 287: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 288: Duck Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 289: Bubble Pond Bridge, 1928 (Box 1)
  - 290: Bubble Pond Bridge, 1928 (Box 1)
  - 291: Bubble Pond Bridge, 1928 (Box 1)
  - 292: Bubble Pond Bridge (Box 1)
  - 293: Bubble Pond Bridge, 1928 (Box 1)
  - 294: Eagle Lake Road underpass bridge, Eagle Lake-Breakneck-Witch Hole horse road. (Box 1)
  - 295: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 296: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 297: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 298: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 299: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 300: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 301: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 302: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 303: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 304: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 305: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 306: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 307: Stanley Brook Bridge. Stanley Brook Road-Bar Hill-Day Mountain horse road underpass bridge. (Box 1)
  - 308: Stanley Brook Bridge. Detail of stone masonry. (Box 1)
  - 309: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 310: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 311: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 312: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 313: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 314: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 315: Stanley Brook Bridge. (Box 1)
  - 316: Jordan Pond carriage road gate house. Paul D. Simpson and family lived here for nine years. (Box 1)
  - 317: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 318: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 319: Jordan Pond gatehouse. (Box 1)
  - 321: Paul D. Simpson, engineer of carriage roads and bridges, with son Chip, 1933 (Box 1)
  - 322: Charles Stoughton, with Chip Simpson (Stoughton designed eight of the carriage road bridges)., 1931 (Box 1)
  - 323: Paul D. Simpson with two unidentified men. (Box 1)
  - 324: Unidentified man on running board of car. (Box 1)
  - 325: Paul D. Simpson with son, Chip, 1929 (Box 1)
  - 326: Mr. Stoughton with Chip at Seal Harbor, 1930 (Box 1)
  - 327: Two men and one boy, all unidentified, at overlook. (Box 1)
  - 328: Jordan Pond with the Bubbles beyond. (Box 1)
  - 329: Stream (Box 1)